(Sheldon:)I'm sensing awkwardness,
am I right?
(Howard:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Swish.
(Bernadette:)I don't want to be pushy,
(Bernadette:)but you've never done
pharmaceutical sales before.
(Bernadette:)It seems like you could use
this time to get a head start.
PENNY: Well, the first few
weeks will be all training.
(Penny:)They'll tell me everything
I need to know.
(Bernadette:)But imagine how impressed
they'd be if you showed up
(Bernadette:)already familiar
with the material.
(Penny:)Okay, so what, you want me
to be like a teacher's pet?
(Bernadette:)Couldn't hurt.
LEONARD:
Mm, I don't know.
(Leonard:)Who here has ever been hurt
(Leonard:)because they were
the teacher's pet?
(Sheldon:)It was like the rest of
the class wanted Ms. McDonald
(Sheldon:)to forget the quiz.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪